Brian Zauner

binrz00@hotmail.com

612-720-5686

https://github.com/binrz00

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I have been a line cook for 13 years, and a commercial fisherman for 4 seasons. I recently completed a full stack web development course. I have made some offline apps to make book keeping easier for the boats I have worked on and I am ready to make bigger and better apps to benefit my future employers. I bring a strong work ethic to every job I take, and I always leave a company better than when I first arrived. I can identify an issue before it becomes a problem. I can work well with all different personalities. I also usually improve efficiency in any working environment.

SKILLS

I am proficient in HTML, JavaScript, CSS, SQL and non-SQL databases, node, express, react, and offline databases. I also have experience using C++, PHP, and various frameworks for script and CSS.

EXPERIENCE

Crew Member John Perkins Enterprises – Sweet, Idaho | August 2016 – October 2020

- Provided reports and other information to managers and Alaska Fish and Game
- Monitored tanks and controlled filling
- Prepared for docking and departures
- Light crane operations
- Navigation and maneuvering from Dutch Harbor, Alaska through Canada, and down to Seattle,
 Washington
- Performed all duties requested by the captain

Crew Member Kirsten Marie Tendering – Seattle, Washington | May 2019 – August 2020

- Provided reports and other information to managers and Alaska Fish and Game
- Prepared for docking and departures

- Light crane operations
- Managed food, fish, and net accounts for all the gillnetters in the district
- Navigate and maneuver from the fishery to the plant
- Navigate and maneuver from Seattle, Washington through Canada, and up to Bristol Bay, Alaska
- Performed all duties requested by the captain

Lead line cook The Grumpy Minnow Center City – Center City, MN | January 2019 – May 2019

- Collaborated with the head chef to discuss menu items and executions
- Prepared food orders following food safety protocols
- Managed cleaning and sanitation of the work area before leaving
- Assisted in the line configuration for optimized food service
- Prepared food before service for optimized food service

Line Cook Aqua Forest Lake – Forest Lake, MN | September 2018 – January 2018

- Received orders, prepared, and delivered quality food
- Cleaned and sanitized work area and utensils
- Prepared food beforehand to expedite food service
- Stocked the kitchen when the food order arrived
- Followed all rules and regulations for safe food handling

EDUCATION

Coding boot camp certificate University of Minnesota | Minneapolis, MN | February 2020